Greater Hartford Jewish Community Center Collection 0008.120.001
Jewish Historical Society of Greater Hartford
Greater Hartford Jewish Community Center
1950-2010
0008.120.001
Jewish Historical Society of Greater Hartford
8.0 Cubic feet 18 standard size document boxes and 7 boxes of photographs
The local "Y" groups, however, disbanded in the late 1930s. Concerned for local youth, B'nai B'rith proposed in 1938 the formation of a community center, but it was not until 1942 that a Jewish Center Association was organized. Under the sponsorship of the United Jewish Social Service and the Community Chest, recreational programs were provided on Vine Street.
In 1948, the Jewish Federation, which had been organized in 1945, purchased a building on Asylum Avenue for a Community Center. Initially the Center concentrated on youth recreation at the Center itself, but gradually it expanded to a summer camp and activities for adults of all ages. In 1959, with an expanding membership and the westward movement of the Jewish population, the Community Center began planning for a new home. The Jewish Community Center on Bloomfield Avenue, designed by internationally acclaimed architect Walter Gropius, was completed in 1962. A major building addition was added in 1990.
Scope and Contents note
Box 1: Adult Education
Adult Education/Adult Education Committee, 1995
Adult Education/Adult Education Committee/Jewish Enrichment Committee, 1980s-1990s
Adult Education/Courses
Adult Education/Co-wed club
Adult Education/Multicultural programs
Adult Education/Hebrew classes
Adult Education/Holiday events/Chanukah
Adult Education/Holiday events/Miscellaneous
Adult Education/Holiday events/Passovers
Adult Education/Holiday events/Purim
Adult Education/Holiday events/Rosh Hashanah
Adult Education/Holiday events/Tu Ba'shvat
Adult Education/Jewish birth baskets
Adult Education/Kolot (Choir)
Adult Education/Kosher Culinary Institute
Adult Education/Lectures
Adult Education/Miscellaneous
Adult Education/New Mothers' group
Adult Education/Sabbath
Adult Education/Saturday Eve-ers
Adult Education/Synagogue and Jewish Organization Fair, 1989
Adult Education/Travel
Adult Education/Yiddish Cultural Club
Adult Education/Yiddish Programs
Adult Education/Yom Hashoah (Holocaust Remembrance Day)
Adult Education/Young Adults and Singles
Box 2: Cultural Arts
Cultural Arts (Including Ann Randall Committee)/Art Exhibits. See also Sephardic programs.
Cultural Arts (Including Ann Randall Committee)/Art Exhibits
Cultural Arts (Including Ann Randall Committee)/Art Exhibits/Newspaper clippings
Cultural Arts/Art Exhibits, 2000s
Cultural Arts/Art Exhibits/Goldenthal, Jolene, art critic at Hartford Courant/Newspaper articles, 1970-1980
Cultural Arts (Including Ann Randall Committee)/Classes
Cultural Arts (Including Ann Randall Committee)/Concerts
Cultural Arts (Including Ann Randall Committee)/Dance
Cultural Arts (Including Ann Randall Committee)/Fundraising
Cultural Arts (Including Ann Randall Committee)/Jewish Musical Festival
Cultural Arts/Literature
Cultural Arts (Including Ann Randall Committee)/Miscellaneous Events
Cultural Arts (Including Ann Randall Committee)/Poetry
Cultural Arts (Including Ann Randall Committee)/Program Listing
Cultural Arts (Including Ann Randall Committee)/Randall, Ann
Cultural Arts (Including Ann Randall Committee)/Theater and Cinema (includes dvds of plays)
Cultural Arts (Including Ann Randall Committee)/Travel Programs
Cultural Arts/(Including Ann Randall Committee)/Randall, Ann Heilpern, biographical information
Cultural Arts/Committee
Cultural Arts/Hartford Jewish Film festival, 1996-2007
Cultural Arts/Sephardic Programs
Cultural Arts/Tribute to Anne Frank, 1984
Box 3: General Administration
General Administration/Anniversaries/80th, 1995
General Administration/Anniversaries/85th, 1999
General Administration/Anniversaries/Jewish Tercentenary Year, 1954
General Administration/Annual Meeting Invitations
General Administration/Annual Meeting Newspaper clippings
General Administration/Annual Meeting Programs, 1950s
General Administration/Annual Meeting Programs, 1960s
General Administration/Annual Meeting Programs, 1970s
General Administration/Annual Meeting Programs, 1980s
General Administration/Annual Meeting Programs, 1990s
General Administration/Annual Meeting Programs, 2000s
General Administration/Annual Reports, 1990s-2000s
General Administration/Awards
Box 4: General Administration: Board of Directors
General Administration/Board of Directors/Members, see also Annual Meetings
General Administration/Board of Directors/Minutes
General Administration/Board of Directors/Miscellaneous
General Administration/Board of Directors/Planning/1982 Oct., Study of "Directions and Priorities"
General Administration/Board of Directors/Planning/1983 March, Capital Needs Committee Report
General Administration/Board of Directors/Planning/1984 Study under JWB Auspices
General Administration/Board of Directors/Planning/1988 United Way Agency Self-assessment Study
General Administration/Board of Directors/Planning/1990 member and Community Survey
General Administration/Board of Directors/Planning/SWOT Analysis, 2002
General Administration/Board of Directors/Policies/Miscellaneous
General Administration/Board of Directors/Policies/Saturday (Shabbat) Opening, 1962
General Administration/Board of Directors/Policies/Saturday (Shabbat) opening, 1981
General Administration/Board of Directors/Policies/Saturday (Shabbat) Opening, 1992-1994
General Administration/Board of Directors/Policies/Saturday (Shabbat) Opening, 2007
General Administration/Board of Directors/Presidents
Box 5: General Administration: Buildings
General Administration/Buildings/1015 Asylum Ave., Hartford, 1949
General Administration/Buildings/335 Bloomfield Ave, W. H., 1962, 3 folders
General Administration/Buildings/335 Bloomfield Ave., W. Hartford/Plans
General Administration/Buildings/335 Bloomfield Ave, W. H. /Expansion, 1990, 2 folders
General Administration/Buildings/335 Bloomfield Ave., W.H./Architects Collaborative/construction reports, 1962
General Administration/Buildings/335 Bloomfield Ave., W.H./Expansion/Groundbreaking, 1989
General Administration/Buildings/335 Bloomfield Ave., W.H./Horn Construction Company/contract and related documents, 1960
General Administration/Buildings/335 Bloomfield Ave., W.H./Planning/Committees, 1960s
General Administration/Buildings/335 Bloomfield Ave., W.H./Planning/Minutes of Meetings, late 1950s-early 1960s
General Administration/Buildings/335 Bloomfield Ave., W.H./Scrapbook about planning and construction, 1960s
Box 6: General Administration: Buildings
General Administration/Buildings/335 Bloomfield Ave, W. H. /Second renovation/2000s
General Administration/Buildings/Mandel building/Fundraising, 2000s
Box 7: General Administration: C – F
General Administration/Calendar
General Administration/Constitution and By-Laws
General Administration/Financial Records, 1980s
General Administration/Financial Records, 1990s
General Administration/Financial Records, 2000s
General Administration/Founding
General Administration/Fundraising/Annual Scholarship and Gala/1980s
General Administration/Fundraising/Annual Scholarship and Gala/1990s
General Administration/Fundraising/Annual Scholarship and Gala/2000s
General Administration/Fundraising/Annual Scholarship Fund/Taste of the Town, 2000s
General Administration/Fundraising/Building Campaign, 1986-1990, 2 folders
General Administration/Fundraising/Leadership
General Administration/Fundraising/Miscellaneous
Box 8: General Administration: G - Z
General Administration/Historical Highlights
General Administration/JWB and JCC Association Magazines
General Administration/Membership/Membership Studies
General Administration/Membership/Miscellaneous
General Administration/Membership/Promotional Materials
General Administration/Miscellaneous
General Administration/Mission Statements
General Administration/Program and Administrative Studies, 1950s-1960s
General Administration/Public Relations and Marketing
General Administration/Staff/Minutes and Memos
General Administration/Staff/Job Descriptions
General Administration/Staff Members/Jacobs, David L.
General Administration/Staff Members/Kaplan, Theodore N.
General Administration/Staff Members/Leipzig, Jay
General Administration/Staff Members/Margolis, Jed
General Administration/Staff Members/Marks, Sheila
General Administration/Staff Members/Miscellaneous
General Administration/Staff Members/Newman, Brian
General Administration/Staff Members/Shapiro, Murray
General Administration/Staff Members/Wyckoff, Karen
General Administration/Volunteers
Box 9: Health and Fitness
This series includes documentation of the many sports, physical fitness, and mental health services offered by the GHJCC.
Health and Fitness/GHJCC Swim and Tennis Club
Health and Fitness/Maccabi Games, 1997
Health and Fitness/Maccabi Games/Miscellaneous
Health and Fitness/Miscellaneous
Health and fitness/Surveys and planning, 1980s
Box 10: Program Catalogs, 1940s-1980
Program Catalogs/1940s-1950s
Program Catalogs/1963-1964
Program Catalogs/1964-1965
Program Catalogs/1967-1968
Program Catalogs/1968-1969
Program Catalogs/1969-1970
Program Catalogs/1970-1971
Program Catalogs/1971-1972
Program Catalogs/1972-1973
Program Catalogs/1973-1974
Program Catalogs/1974-1975
Program Catalogs/1975-1976
Program Catalogs/1976-1977
Program Catalogs/1977-1978
Program Catalogs/1978-1979
Program Catalogs/1979-1980
Box 11: Program Catalogs, 1980s - 1990s
Program Catalogs/1980-1981
Program Catalogs/1981-1982
Program Catalogs/1982-1983
Program Catalogs/1983-1984
Program Catalogs/1984-1985
Program Catalogs/1985-1986
Program Catalogs/1986-1987
Program Catalogs/1987-1988
Program Catalogs/1988
Program Catalogs/1989-1990
Program Catalogs/1992, no catalog, newspaper clippings only
Program Catalogs/1995
Program Catalogs/1996
Program Catalogs/1997
Program Catalogs/1998
Program Catalogs/1999
Box 12: Program Catalogs, 2000s
Program Catalogs/2000
Program Catalogs/2001
Program Catalogs/2001-2002
Program Catalogs/2002-2003
Program Catalogs/2003
Program Catalogs/2004
Program Catalogs/2005
Box 13: Senior Adults, A-N
Senior Adults/Activities and Programs, 1950s-1970s
Senior Adults/Activities and Programs, 1980s-1990s
Senior Adults/Community Action Committee, 1970s
Senior Adults/Eastern Suburbs
Senior Adults/Education Programs
Senior Adults/Escort Project, 1978
Senior Adults/Extension Programs and Sites, 1960s-1970s
Senior Adults/Forms/Miscellaneous
Senior Adults/Friendly Social Club/Constitution
Senior Adults/Friendly Social Club/Members
Senior Adults/Friendly Social Club/Miscellaneous
Senior Adults/Friendly Social Club/Newsletter, 1957-1968
Senior Adults/Friendly Social Club/Newsletter, 1974-1978
Senior Adults/Friendly Social Club/Officers, 1970s
Senior Adults/Friendly Social Club/Programs, 1959-1985
Senior Adults/Friendly Social Club/Scrapbook, 1955-1977 OVERSIZE
Senior Adults/Gym and Swim Program
Senior Adults/Health Services
Senior Adults/Historical Highlights
Senior Adults/Intergenerational programs
Senior Adults/Leisure Lounge
Senior Adults/Men's Club
Senior Adults/Miscellaneous
Senior Adults/New Britain Seniors/Miscellaneous
Senior Adults/New Britain Seniors/Newsletter, 1970s-80s
Senior Adults/Newcomers Group
Box 14: Senior Adults, O-Z
Senior Adults/Older Adult Program/Committee/Members, 1970s
Senior Adults/Older Adult Program/Minutes, 1974-1979
Senior Adults/Older Adult Program/Minutes, 1980s
Senior Adults/Older Adult Program/Newsletter, 1957-1959
Senior Adults/Older Adult Program/Newsletter, 1979-1981
Senior Adults/Older Adult Program/Planning and Budgets, 1970s-1980s
Senior Adults/Older Adult Program/Reports and Evaluations, 1950s-1960s
Senior Adults/Older Adult Program/Reports and Evaluations, 1980s
Senior Adults/Older Adult Program/Registration Forms, 1965-1968
Senior Adults/Planning/Studies
Senior Adults/Retired Seniors Council
Senior Adults/Scrapbooks/Box 15:
Senior Adults/Older Adult Program/Scrapbook, 1964-1965
Senior Adults/Older Adult Program/Scrapbook, 1966-1967
Senior Adults/Older Adult Program/Scrapbook, 1968-1969
Senior Adults/Older Adult Program/Scrapbook, 1967-1968
Senior Adults/Older Adult Program/Scrapbook, 1968-1969
Senior Adults/ S-Z Box 16:
Senior adults/Senior Breakfast Club
Senior Adults/Senior Housing, 1970s
Senior Adults/Senior Power/Members, 1970s
Senior Adults/Senior Power/Miscellaneous, 1970s
Senior Adults/Senior Power/Newsletter, 1970s
Senior Adults/Senior Volunteer Corps/Miscellaneous
Senior Adults/SES/Constitution and By-laws
Senior Adults/SES/members, 1960s-1970s
Senior Adults/SES/Minutes, 1974
Senior Adults/SES/minutes, 1975
Senior Adults/SES/Minutes, 1976-1977
Senior Adults/SES/Minutes, 1977-1978
Senior Adults/SES/Miscellaneous, 1974
Senior Adults/SES/Newsletter, 1974-1978
Senior Adults/SES/Officers, 1970s
Senior Adults/SES/Play scripts, 1970s
Senior Adults/SES/Programs, 1970s-1980s
Senior Adults/SES II/Constitution and By-Laws, 1978
Senior Adults/SES II/Members, 1970s
Senior Adults/SES II/Minutes, 1974-1975
Senior Adults/SES II/Minutes, 1977-1977
Senior Adults/SES II/Minutes, 1977-1978
Senior Adults/SES II/Miscellaneous, 1970s
Senior Adults/SES II/Newsletter, 1975-1978
Senior Adults/Singles
Senior Adults/Staff, 1970s
Senior Adults/Sunday for Seniors, 1970s-1980s
Senior Adults/Telephone Reassurance Program, 1977
Senior Adults/Theater program/Correspondence, 1970s
Senior Adults/Theater program/programs, 1970s
Senior Adults/Theater program/publicity, 1970s-1980
Senior Adults/Theater program/schedule, 1970-1980s
Senior Adults/Transportation, 1970s
Senior Adults/Travel, 1974-1981
Senior Adults/Travel, 1990s-2000s
Senior Adults/Volunteers/miscellaneous
Small Series Box 17
This box contains GHJCC series for which the JHSGH only holds a few folders.
Miscellaneous newspaper clippings
Book festival
Book festival, 2006
Book festival 2011, 10 year anniversary (includes 2 DVDs)
Camp Shalom and Camp Keshet/Miscellaneous
Camp Shalom and Camp Keshet/Newspaper clippings
Camp Shalom and Camp Keshet/Publicity and Catalogs
Committees/New Leadership, 1980s
Early Childhood Center/Camp Rennah, Campareenah
Early Childhood Center/Miscellaneous
Early Childhood Center/Newspaper clippings, 2000s
Holocaust Events sponsored by JCC (see also JHSGH's Holocaust Collection
Interfaith programs
Israel Affairs/Halimi, Ilan/vigil, 2006
Israel Affairs/Israel's 30th anniversary, 1978
Israel Affairs/Israel's 40th anniversary, 1988
Israel Affairs/Israel's 50th anniversary, 1998
Israel Affairs/Israel's' anniversaries, miscellaneous
Israel Affairs/Israeli Folk Dancing
Israel Affairs/Jerusalem
Israel Affairs/Let's Go Israel
Israel Affairs/Miscellaneous
Israel Affairs/Shaliach
Israel Affairs/Yom Ha'atzmaut (Independence Day)
Israel Affairs/Yom Hazikaron (Israel Remembrance Day)
Maccabean Games
Race Relations
Shabbat, 1980s
Security
September 11, 2001/Responses and Memorials
Soviet Jewry/Miscellaneous
Special Needs/Miscellaneous
Youth Services/children (see also Adult Education/Holidays)
Youth Services/College Students
Youth Services/Jonathan's Dream playground (Barzach-Jaffe family, boundless playgrounds)
Youth Services/Teens (see also Cultural Arts/Theater and Cinema)
Newsletters: Box 18
Newsletters/JCC Journal/1940s
Newsletters/Scope/1950s
Newsletters/Scope/1960s
Newsletters/Scope/1970 1973
Newsletters/Scope/1974 1976
Newsletters/Center Fold/1977 May - 1979
Newsletters/Center Fold/1980 1984
Newsletters/1985 1989
Newsletters/OnCenter/before 2000/OVERSIZE: Box 1
Newsletters/OnCenter/2000s/OVERSIZE: Box 2
Artifacts:
Paperweight, 1989, in miscellaneous artifact box with Hart family artifacts, etc.
Photographs
The GHJCC photographs collection documents a wide variety of religious, social, recreational and cultural activities. Both adult and youth activities are included. Most of the photographs in this collection were taken during the 1980s.
Photos: Box 1: Camps: Keshet, Macabee, Moshava, Naomi, Reenah, Shalom, New Hartford
Note, in 1978, Camp Sholom moved from New Hartford to Windsor and changed its name to Camp Shalom.
Camps/Camp Keshet
Camps/Camp Macabee
Camps/Camp Moshava
Camps/Camp Naomi
Camps/Camp Reenah, Campareenah see GHJCC/Early Childhood Center
Camps/Camp Shalom, New Hartford/(see also photos/organizations/Jewish Children's Service Organization
Camps/Camp Shalom, New Hartford/Administration and Staff
Camps/Camp Shalom, New Hartford/Activities/Boating
Camps/Camp Shalom, New Hartford/Activities/Buildings and Grounds
Camps/Camp Shalom, New Hartford/Activities/Carnival
Camps/Camp Shalom, New Hartford/Activities/Crafts
Camps/Camp Shalom, New Hartford/Flood Damage
Camps/Camp Shalom, New Hartford/Fundraising
Camps/Camp Shalom, New Hartford/Fundraising
Camps/Camp Shalom, New Hartford/Miscellaneous, 3 folders
Camps/Camp Shalom, New Hartford/Activities/Nature
Camps/Camp Shalom, New Hartford/Activities/Swimming
Photos: Box 1a: Camps: Shalom, Windsor
Camps/Camp Shalom, Windsor/Administration
Camps/Camp Shalom, Windsor/Activities/Animals
Camps/Camp Shalom, Windsor/Activities/Archery
Camps/Camp Shalom, Windsor/Activities/Baseball
Camps/Camp Shalom, Windsor/Activities/Boating and River Sports
Camps/Camp Shalom, Windsor/Activities/Campfires and Cookouts
Camps/Camp Shalom, Windsor/Activities/Carnival
Camps/Camp Shalom, Windsor/Activities/Crafts
Camps/Camp Shalom, Windsor/Activities/Horseback Riding
Camps/Camp Shalom, Windsor/Activities/Jewish Rituals
Camps/Camp Shalom, Windsor/Activities/Miscellaneous - sports
Camps/Camp Shalom, Windsor/Activities/Miscellaneous, 3 folders
Camps/Camp Shalom, Windsor/Activities/Ropes course
Camps/Camp Shalom, Windsor/Activities/Swimming
Camps/Camp Shalom, Windsor/Activities/Tennis
Camps/Camp Shalom, Windsor/Activities/Theatrics
Camps/Camp Shalom, Windsor/Activities/Windsor
Camps/Camp Shalom, Windsor/Buildings and Grounds
Camps/Camp Shalom, Windsor/Donors
Camps/Camp Shalom, Windsor/Fundraising
Camps/Camp Shalom, Windsor/Staff and Counselors
Camps/Miscellaneous
Photos: Box 2: Adult Education, Book Festival, Cultural Arts
Adult Education/Bridge Classes
Adult Education/College Age
Adult Education/Holidays/Chanukah
Adult Education/Holidays/High Holy Days
Adult Education/Holidays/Pesach
Adult Education/Holidays/Purim
Adult Education/Holidays/Sukkoth
Adult Education/Miscellaneous, three folders
Adult Education/Singles and Young Adults
Adult Education/Soviet Jewry
Adult Education/Yom Hashoah
Book Festival
Cultural Arts/Art Classes
Cultural Arts/Art Exhibits
Cultural Arts/Concerts
Cultural Arts/Dance
Cultural Arts/Gala
Cultural Arts/Jewish Music Festival
Cultural Arts/Miscellaneous
Cultural Arts/Ann Randall Committee/Theater/Center Players, undated and 1950s
Cultural Arts/Ann Randall Committee/Theater/Center Players, 1960s
Cultural Arts/Ann Randall Committee/Theater/Center Players, 1970s
Cultural Arts/Ann Randall Committee/Theater/Center Players, 1980s
Cultural Arts/Ann Randall Committee/Theater/Center Players, 1990s
Cultural Arts/Local Theater/2007
Cultural Arts/Professional Companies
Cultural Arts/Travel
Photos: Box 3: Health and Fitness, Israel Affairs, Special Needs
Health and Fitness/Adult Programs/Classes
Health and Fitness/Adult Programs/Fitness rooms and health club
Health and Fitness/Adult Programs/Runners and Joggers
Health and Fitness/Pool
Health and Fitness/Miscellaneous
Health and Fitness/Racquetball
Health and Fitness/Youth Programs/Classes
Health and Fitness/Youth Programs/Maccabi Games
Health and Fitness/Youth Programs/Miscellaneous
Health and Fitness/Israel Affairs/Folk dancing
Health and Fitness/Israel Affairs/Folk dancing/Or Chadash
Health and Fitness/Youth Programs/Preschool
Health and Fitness/Youth Programs/Swimming
Health and Fitness/Youth Programs/Teams
Israel Affairs/Israel Teen visitors
Isreal Affairs/Iztak Rabin visits JCC 1977
Israel Affairs/Let's Go Israel
Israel Affairs/Miscellaneous
Israel Affairs/Shaliach
Israel Affairs/Trips
Israel Affairs/Walkathon
Israel Affairs/Yom Haatzmaut (Independence Day)
Israel Affairs/Yom Hazikaron (Remembrance Day)
Special Needs/Athletics
Special Needs/Sunday Afternoon Group
Photos: Box 4: Senior Adults
Senior Adults/Arts and Crafts
Senior Adults/Bingo and Cards
Senior Adults/Choraliers
Senior Adults/Education
Senior Adults/Extension programs and sites
Senior Adults/folk dancing
Senior Adults/Fundraising
Senior Adults/gym and swim program
Senior Adults/Health Services
Senior Adults/Holiday Programs/B'Nai b'rith Chanukah Party
Senior Adults/Holiday Programs/Chanukah parties/sponsor unknown
Senior Adults/Holiday Programs/NCJW Chanukah Luncheons
Senior Adults/Holiday Programs/Miscellaneous
Senior Adults/Lieberman, Joseph, visit, 1980
Senior Adults/Miscellaneous, pre-1962
Senior Adults/Miscellaneous, post-1962, 2 folders
Senior Adults/Programs with children
Senior Adults/Staff training
Senior Adults/theater
Senior Adults/travel
Senior Adults/volunteers assisting with mailings
Box 5: General Administration
General Administration/Anniversaries/80th
General Administration/Annual Meetings
General Administration/Board of Directors/Members
General Administration/Board Members/Active lay members
General Administration/Buildings/91 Vine Street, Hartford
General Administration/Buildings/1015 Asylum Ave., Hartford, 1949
General Administration/Buildings/335 Bloomfield Ave., West Hartford, 1962
General Administration/Buildings/335 Bloomfield Ave., West Hartford/General
General Administration/Buildings/335 Bloomfield Ave., West Hartford/Field House/Groundbreaking, 2006
Administration/Buildings/335 Bloomfield Ave., West Hartford/expansion, 1990
General Administration/Buildings/Sculpture and Art/Holocaust Memorial
General Administration/Buildings/Fundraising/Annual Scholarship Fund Gala, 1983
General Administration/Buildings/Fundraising/Annual Scholarship Fund Gala, 1984
General Administration/Buildings/Fundraising/Annual Scholarship Fund Gala, 1985
General Administration/Buildings/Fundraising/Annual Scholarship Fund Gala, 1986
General Administration/Buildings/Fundraising/Annual Scholarship Fund Gala, 1987
General Administration/Buildings/Fundraising/Annual Scholarship Fund Gala, 1988
General Administration/Buildings/Fundraising/Annual Scholarship Fund Gala, 1989
Box 6: General Administration
General Administration/Buildings/Fundraising/Annual Scholarship Fund Gala, 1990
General Administration/Buildings/Fundraising/Annual Scholarship Fund Gala, 1991
General Administration/Buildings/Fundraising/Annual Scholarship Fund Gala, 1992
General Administration/Buildings/Fundraising/Annual Scholarship Fund Gala, 1993
General Administration/Buildings/Fundraising/Annual Scholarship Fund Gala, 1994
General Administration/Buildings/Fundraising/Annual Scholarship Fund Gala, 1995
General Administration/Buildings/Fundraising/Annual Scholarship Fund Gala, 1996
General Administration/Buildings/Fundraising/Annual Scholarship Fund Gala, 1997
General Administration/Buildings/Fundraising/Annual Scholarship Fund Gala, undated
General Administration/Staff
General Administration/Staff and lay
General Administration/members and membership
Box 7: Early Childhood Center
Early Childhood Center, undated
Early Childhood Center, 1950s
Early Childhood Center, 1960s
Early Childhood Center, 1970s-1980s
Early Childhood Center, 1970-1974
Early Childhood Center, 1975-1979
Early Childhood Center, 1980s
Early Childhood Center, 1990s
Early Childhood Center/Campareenah, undated
Early Childhood Center/Campareenah, 1950s
Early Childhood Center/Campareenah,, 1960s
Early Childhood Center/Campareenah, 1970s
Early Childhood Center/Campareenah, 1980s
Early Childhood Center/Campareenah, 1990s
Box 8: Youth Services
Youth Services/Athletic programs
Youth Services/Children/Dance
Youth Services/Children/Entertainment programs
Youth Services/Children/Holidays
Youth Services/Children/Jonathan's Dream playground (Barzach family)
Youth Services/Children/Miscellaneous, 2 folders
Youth Services/Children/Theater
Youth Services/"Junior Debs"